Guide to the Yale Daily News Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Daily News photographs
1950-2001
RU 693
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
48
(71 boxes)
The materials consist primarily of photographic negatives used in the Yale Daily News. Subjects cover all aspects of Yale student life, including athletics and student demonstrations.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Related Materials
Yale Daily News Records (RU 888). Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist primarily of photographic negatives used in the Yale Daily News. Subjects cover all aspects of Yale student life, including athletics and student demonstrations.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
College student newspapers and periodicals; Journalism, College; Negatives (photographs); Photographs; Yale daily news; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, 1957-1982; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1941-1970
    - 1941 Dec 6, Front Page, 1941 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1941 Dec 8, Front Page, 1941 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1957 April 20
      - Baseball v. Army, 1957 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1958 March 12
      - Baseball Mugs, 1958 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1960 October 2
      - Football V. Coastguard, 1960 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1962 May - December 12
      - Track, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Baseball, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Varsity Lecture, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Football V. Brown, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Football v. Colgate, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Wartes from Marry's, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1963 February - November 15
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Lacrosse Mugs, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Bicycle Race, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Presidents Play, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Staten Is. Ferry, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - World Cry, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1964 January 13 - December 14
      - Freshman Play, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Swimming Mugs, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Hockey v. N. Eastern, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Basketball v. U Conn, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Swimming v. Springfield, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Cornell Freshman Football, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Yale v. Dartmouth, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Yale v. Columbia, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Rifle Team, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Basketball Mugs, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Trumbull Beer and Bike, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - YVSH, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Wrestling Mugs, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Yale Cycle Team, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Blood Drive, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1965 January 1 - December 15
      - Push-up Record, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Basketball, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Swimming Eastern Collegiate Championships, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Hockey v. All Star, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Track, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Freshman Football, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Debate, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1968 January 27 - February 2
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1969 January 28 - October 20
      - Swimming v. Colgate, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Swimming Mugs, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Hockey v. Colgate, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Football scrimmage w/ Trinity, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Alex Ponti in the Soccer nets, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Football v. Colgate, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Football v. Brown, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Soccer v. Bridgeport, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Jay Lee Football v. Coast Guard, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1969 October 25 - December 18
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - The Game, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hockey v. St. Nick's, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hockey, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hockey v. Colgate, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hockey v. U Mass, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Swimming v. Monmouth, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Wrestling v. Rutgers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Wrestling v. Central Conn, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Swimming v. Cornell, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Fencing v. NYU, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hockey v. RPI, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1970 January 28
      - Wrestling v. Springfield, 1970 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Swimming v. Colgate, 1970 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1970 February 3-28
      - Wrestling v. West Point, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Squash, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Track v. Dartmouth, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Fencing, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Swimming v. Springfield, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Wrestling v. Princeton, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1970 March 1 - April 25
      - Swimming v. Navy, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Judo, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Swimming v. Harvard, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Free-throw Finals, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Wrestling Dinner at DKE, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Lacrosse v. Wesleyan, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Baseball v. Dartmouth, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1970 September 9-30
      - Soccer scrimmage v. New Haven, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Soccer, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Yale Football, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Fencing Team, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Day care, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Open School for Tuesday, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Yale Symphony, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Fire Safety Marshall, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1970 October 3-21
      - Football v. Colgate, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Football v. Brown, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Pharmacist at Liggett's, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Water Polo Practice, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Volleyball, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Smog, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Sculptor at work, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Poison Ivy, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Evicted Dry Cleaner, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Man from N.A.S.A., 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Fake Goodyear Blimp, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - White's new look, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Admissions dept., 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Macy's Christmas display, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Sideburn Shots, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - English Folk Dance, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1970 November 2-23
      - Hockey Practice, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Penn Football, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Touch Football, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Princeton Football, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Soccer v. U Conn, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - The Game, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Freshman v. Scrimmage, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Bicycle Wheel (minus bike), 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Book, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Silver, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Musical instruments, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1970 December 1-23
      - Hockey Simulation for Program, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Fencing, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Hockey v. N Eastern, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - U Conn basketball, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Freshman Hockey Team, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Varsity Hockey Team, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Two Artists, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Lettuce boycott, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Dariton Death (play), 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1971
    - 1971 January 5-23
      - Hockey v. Clarkson Periods, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Hockey v. Army, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Squash v. Army, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Track v. Penn and Brown, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Women's Swimming v. U Mass and Army, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Basketball v. Colgate, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Shoplifting, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Money Winner, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Windy Day, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Insider's Guide to Colleges, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1971 February 3-24
      - Wrestling v. Brown, 1971 February (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Freshman Basketball v. U Conn, 1971 February (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Wrestling v. Columbia, 1971 February (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1971 February (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1971 March 2 - April 30
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Basketball v. Army, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Lacrosse practice, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Freshman Baseball v. Quinnipiac, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Baseball v. NYU, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Baseball, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Rugby, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Shoplifting, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Hungry Charlie's Reopen, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Calvin Hill Day Care Center, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Poster, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Prom, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Berkeley gambling casino, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Swimming Carnival, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Grad Student Lounge Construction, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Swimming v. U Conn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Freshman Hockey, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Wrestling v. Harvard, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Female Wrestling Manager, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Indoor Track v. Cornell, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Swimming v. Penn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Hockey v. Fairfield, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Fencing v. Holy Cross, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Swimming v. Springfield, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Harden Redevelopment, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Fencing v. Penn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Future Form, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - J.C.C. Panel, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Indian Dance, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Hungry Charlie's Strike, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Mexican Night-Morse, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - New College Colloquium, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Yale College Course of Study Committee, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Building from whence a worker fell, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Yale Marching Band, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Berkeley-Calhoun Olympics, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1971 May 2 - September 28
      - Freshman Lacrosse v. U Conn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Tennis, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Tennis v. Dartmouth, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Tennis v. Penn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Baseball v. New Haven, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Pre-season Football, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Football v. SCSC, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Soccer Practice, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Football Kickers, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Auto Mechanics Class, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - D.U.H. tour, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Moving in, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Trees (dead and alive), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - U.S.M.C. band, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Grad. student Senate, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Law School, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Heat, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1971 October 1-31
      - Soccer v. Bridgeport, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - JV Football v. Army, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Colgate Football, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Football v. Penn, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Football v. Brown, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Trumbull touch football, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Football Practice, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Soccer, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Women's Field Hockey, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Symphony (Mahler), 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Dahl Committee in Yale (panel with VIP), 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Columbus Day Parade, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Rosenbloom, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Man in a box on York Street, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - U.S.C. interview, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Dartmouth Bonfire, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1971 November 6-29
      - Football v. Penn, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Hockey v. St. Nick's, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Clowns, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Y.N.F.A.C. voting, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Circus, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - New Haven meeting- parking garage, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1971 December 1-19
      - Basketball v. Fordham, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Hockey v. U Conn, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Hockey v. N Eastern, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Basketball v. Oklahoma City College, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Squash v. Stony Brook, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Wrestling v. U Mass, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Swimming v. Cornell, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Wrestling v. East Rutgers, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Swimming v. Florida, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Fencing v. West Point, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Yale moot court, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Duplicate bridge, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Christmas tree on Green, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Kline Christmas Tree, 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1972
    - 1972 January 3-31
      - Hockey v. Middleburg, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Freshman Hockey v. Hotchkiss, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Basketball v. Australian National Team, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - JV Polo v. Harvard, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Freshman Football v. New Haven Univ., 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Fencing, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Dada Collection by Hans Richter, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Flu at DUH, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - De Vane Lecture, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - ZPG Debate, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - TA's meeting, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1972 February 2-27
      - Indoor Track v. Harvard, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Wet Paint Signs/Bladderball, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - JV Hockey v. Taft, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Fencing v. Trinity, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Hockey v. St. Engalls, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Fencing, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Swimming, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Polo, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Track v. Dartmouth, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Fencing v. Holy Cross, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Polo v. UVA, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Swimming v. Springfield, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Sam Chaunery, Hockey Coach, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Wrestling v. Princeton, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Art show, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Symphony Concert, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - One-Eyed Jack, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Yale Concert Band, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - College guard, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - (Commons?), 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - New Haven Arena, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1972 March 1-18
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Eastern Swimming Championships, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Lacrosse v. CW Post, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Lacrosse v. Johns Hopkins, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Inst. of Human Relations, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Registrars file, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Small stand sculpture, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Parade and garbage cans, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Guards-Colleges, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - AandA bomb scare, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Conn. Alumni meeting, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1972 April 1-29
      - Baseball v. Princeton, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Baseball v. NYU, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Lacrosse v. Williams, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Baseball v. Army, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Baseball v. GW, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Baseball v. Springfield, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Freshman Lacrosse, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Lacrosse v. Mass, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Gilbert (swimmer), 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Faculty Basketball, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Freshman Baseball v. U of Bridgeport, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Lacrosse v. Rutgers, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Lacrosse v. Brown, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Lacrosse v. Dartmouth, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Track, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Lacrosse v. Australia, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - JV Tennis v. Staples High School, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Tennis v. Columbia, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Table Tennis Tournament Final, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Master's Aid, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Fellowship, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - (Coelacanth?), 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Poynter Fellows (ca TV), 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Worker's Pictures, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Tree spraying, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1972 May 3-13
      - Lacrosse v. S. Conn, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Yale Handball Champ, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Lacrosse, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - 1971-72 Yale Handball Champ, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Standing alone baseball in rain, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - 270 Crown Street, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 1972 September 12
      - Varsity Football, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Football assistant coach Wickeshaw, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Football Scrimmage v. Dartmouth, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Soccer, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Soccer v. Conn, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Football v. Conn, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Gym tour, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 1972 October 7-28
      - Football v. Colgate, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Women's Field Hockey, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Football v. Brown, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Field Hockey v. Wesleyan, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Soccer v. Bridgeport, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Columbia Football, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Freshman Football v. Cornell, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1972 November 2-29
      - Hockey v. St. Nick's, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Football in Coxe Cage, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Volleyball, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - New Tennis Courts, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Soccer v. Penn, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Football v. Penn, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Water Polo practice, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - H-Y-P X-C (Cross Country?), 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1972 December 2-12
      - Basketball v. U Conn, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Wrestling v. Central Conn, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Polo v. Cornell, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Hockey v. Boston State, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Track v. U Mass, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 1973
    - 1973 January 3-30
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Hockey v. AIC, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Swimming/Diving v. Army, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Wrestling v. Penn, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Girl and type writer, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Studying for exams and other follies, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 35)